hi guys so today first of february
monday
uh great start to the week and to the
month i'm just taking off from
yesterday's video
uh asian equities opened very positive
so from australia china japan korea
taiwan
all of it positive indian markets
extremely positive
we will speak about it separately in
this moment the second half of europe
all positive and our futures
and the nasdaq futures again in this
moment positive
so great start to the week uh hopefully
this trend can continue
and i can i can smell or i can sense
some profits towards the second half of
the week
but this trend needs to continue so
let's just hope
it does uh coming back to india now i
mean
kalki video manikata that budget is a
polarizing uh event
but i mean at least i was not expecting
it will be so polarizing so positive
uh so the sensex is i think uh sensex
and nifty 50 about five percent
the mid cap 50 small cap fifty two three
percent up
and the bank nifty if i'm not mistaken
is like seven or eight percent up so i
mean absolutely ridiculous
every sector i mean if i look at my
stock portfolio
all the banking stocks cement pvr so
cinemas
um just about every sector that you can
think of
was up today so i mean it was difficult
and then i had to stop myself i was like
no i mean
just just wait because anything can
happen tomorrow don't spend all your uh
cash because that's what
the market wants you to do you know
spend everything and buy
buy and invest everything on the same
day so i had to hold myself
uh so i'll just share with you many
trades
because the banking sector is going up
and i think it will continue to go up
uh so i invested in it and i also booked
some profits
uh icici bank uh it hit its 52-week high
today at about 600.
so let me just uh have a look as well
what i did
so yeah icici bank i liquidated at about
600.
uh it's a great stock to have tomorrow
if the market is up
uh icici bank is up i will re-enter it
but i wanted to book my profit
boney b okay my nikki and i just wanted
to book some profits
uh as well and you know use this
positive momentum to my advantage
so icici bank i sold a little bit
straight back of state
bank of india i sold a bit at about 306
and tomorrow i mean my next target sorry
is 328 so if the upward trend continues
i will again
add more tomorrow with a target of about
328.
in the banking stocks i am also holding
access bank
with the target first target is 728 i am
holding federal bank
target is 79 um and bajaj finance
at 5350 that's the target and kotak
my target is about nineteen fifty one
nine five zero
one important bank that i am missing in
this entire thing is hdfc bank
uh i think every person should have hdfc
bank in their portfolio
unfortunately because i am outside of
india i am not able to buy that stock
right now because
i believe that every stock has a quota
of
a number that the number of people
outside of india can buy it so i think
in this moment i am unable to buy it so
if any of you have any similar
experience with this especially outside
india please do share
so how am i compensating this loss of
not having hdfc bank
i am having units of motilal oswal
bank nifty index fund so the name is
self explanatory
and i really recommend it i believe
motila loswell is the only
bank nifty index fund i could be
mistaken but according to me that's the
only one
and of course i cannot own every bank
stock so i own
part of this i i own the index in a way
so i'm holding all the stocks and hdfc
bank i believe is the largest component
of that index fund
so that is something i i recommend as
well so i'm holding that
and i made some additional purchase and
that's today as well so if this upward
trend continues
i mean of course my profits will also
increase and maybe in a week's time or
something if i
if i think that i have a sizable profit
percentile
i will liquidate it as well so i mean
banks are
the flavor of the day and let's see if
it's the flavor of the week
and i will continue to do you know to
update you of whatever progress i make
on the banking stocks
um two more stocks which i sold today uh
one was larsen and two bro
uh i sold it because it is at its 52
week high booked my profits
larsen again is a stock which just needs
to be there in the portfolio that's it
because if
india grows larsen will grow and because
if india grows the infrastructure will
grow
larsen will grow larsen and nada imports
as well
so larson i will just buy it again
tomorrow i booked the profit today
a car stock germany profit booked grasim
again it was that it's not 52 week
almost 52 week high
i think yara's okay level with her uh
yeah around it's at 11 25 and around
yara so penical
so i lost a percentage or two there but
it's fine i booked the profit
and agar
as well so now that's it for now i mean
i will obviously joby many trade liam
school description it was a frenzy today
because
it's very hard to define key you know
money
allocate because we don't have endless
funds right so you have to
at some point decide focus is industry
because in my portfolio every stock is
so of course i will keep you posted on
whatever i do and
if possible please do like and subscribe
and please let me know your comments or
what trades you did today or what
industry
or what sectors you are focusing on i
would love to know and learn as well
so that's it for now guys till tomorrow
see you bye